[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what century did the great Greek philosopher Aristotle live?", "correct_answer": "4th century BC", "incorrect_answers": ["1st century BC", "7th century BC", "10th century BC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What documentary features rugby playing quadriplegics going full tilt boogie for the gold at the 2004 Paraolympic games in Athens?", "correct_answer": "Murderball", "incorrect_answers": ["Just Do It!", "No Obstacle", "Powerball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Era of Good Feeling is generally applied to describe the national mood of the United States during which years?", "correct_answer": "1815 - 1825", "incorrect_answers": ["1783 - 1805", "1805 - 1820", "1825 - 1845"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Warner Brothers highest grossing film of 1954 was about enormous ants that threatened a small town in the USA. What was the title of this movie?", "correct_answer": "Them!", "incorrect_answers": ["Ants!", "Invasion", "Invaders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie, a crushed and dying Steven Boyd hisses to the victorious Jew to seek his family \u201cin the valley of the lepers!\u201d", "correct_answer": "Ben Hur", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fall of the Roman Empire", "Spartacus", "The Ten Commandments"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the villain in the 2008 film The Incredible Hulk?", "correct_answer": "The Abomination", "incorrect_answers": ["The Human Torch", "Cybor", "Dark-Crawler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country gained independence from the UK and France in 1980 and has a national anthem entitled Yumi, Yumi, Yumi?", "correct_answer": "Vanuatu", "incorrect_answers": ["Venezuela", "Virgin Islands", "Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is a polar bears skin?", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["White", "Pink", "Yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do polar bears live in Antarctica?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous mathematician\u2019s main interest was set theory. He is famous for his diagonal method\u201d of proof.", "correct_answer": "Cantor", "incorrect_answers": ["Euler", "Goedel", "Gauss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is Johnnie Walkers jacket?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown", "Pink", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Rat Race, who played the eccentric woman with the squirrels?", "correct_answer": "Kathy Bates", "incorrect_answers": ["Gloria Allred", "Kathleen Marshall", "Jenica Bergere"]}]